你要去哪里 维奥莱特？
Where are you going, Violet?
只是为了摘些花
Just to pick some flowers.
不要走太远
Don't wander too far.
我的野生爱尔兰玫瑰
My wild Irish Rose
生长最甜美的花朵
The sweetest flower that grows
您可以查找所有位置
You may search everywhere
但没有人能与我狂野的爱尔兰玫瑰相比
But none can compare with my wild Irish Rose
哦 你好！
Oh, hi there!
你想要一个吗？
Do you want one?
你想知道我为什么戴这么有趣的帽子吗？
You are wondering why I'm wearing such a funny hat.
我总是戴这顶帽子
I always wear this hat.
这么多 这是我的名字的一部分 现在
So much, that it's a part of my name now.
我的朋友 我最好的朋友
My friends, my very very best friends.
他们只是叫我玫瑰帽子
They just call me Rose the Hat.
它看起来像一顶魔术师的帽子
It looks like a magicians hat.
是的
It is.
这是一顶魔法帽
It's a magic hat.
你想看吗？
Do you wanna see?
我的袖子上什么都没有
Nothing up my sleeves.
我的帽子里什么都没有
Nothing in my hat.
别担心 那是我的朋友
Don't worry, that's my friend.
你错过了窍门
You're missing the trick.
伸进里面
Reach inside.
哇！太漂亮了
Wow! It's so pretty.
因为它很特别
Because it's special.
说到特别
And speaking of special.
你也有点神奇 不是吗？
You are a little magic too, aren't you?
我手中的花是什么颜色的？
The flower in my hand, what color is it?
紫色
Purple.
维奥莱特！像你一样
Violet! Like you.
你不吃花！
You don't eat flowers!
但是你确实.
But you do.
但这些是特别的
But these are special.
亲爱的 是特别的 味道最好
Honey, it's the special ones that taste best.
我应该回到我妈妈家
I should get back to my mom.
不 留下来 呆一会儿 看看更多的魔法
No, stay, stay a while, see more magic.
你是个特别的小东西 不是吗？
You are a special little thing, aren't you?
不 请...
No, please...
嘿 没事的 医生
Hey, it's okay, Doc.
没关系
It's okay.
那里 都干了
There, all dry.
发生了什么事？
What happened?
你必须跟我谈谈 丹尼
You have to talk to me, Danny.
自从我们离开后你没说话...
You haven't talked since we left...
求你了 医生
Please, Doc.
请
Please.
所以
So...
你不说话吧 医生？
You ain't talking, huh, Doc?
我第一次见到你时 也没说太多话
Weren't talking much the first time I met you neither.
你还记得我们第一次真正交谈吗？
You remember the first time we really talked?
当我在你的脑袋里说话的时候
When I spoke up inside your head.
让你感觉很好 对吧？
Made you feel good, right?
知道你并不孤单
Knowing you're not alone.
有人也是为我做的
Someone did that for me too.
有一天 丹尼・托伦斯 你会教别人的
And someday, Danny Torrance, you'll teach someone else.
我不会的
I won't.
不 你不会的 嗯？
No, you won't, huh?
我不会发光的 我是说 别再说了 这很危险
I won't shine, I mean. No more, it's dangerous.
非常好 有时
Very good it is. Sometimes.
她找到我了
She found me.
她会回来回来 直到她得到我
She'll come back and come back until she gets me.
你是对的
You're right.
俯瞰的谴责
The Overlook's condemned.
登上 有饥饿的老鬼在那里 伸手向你
Boarded up, there are starving old ghosts in there, reaching out for you.
也不会停止与她
Won't stop with her, either.
书中的图片
Pictures in the book.
你说他们只是书上的照片 它们不会伤害我
You said they were just pictures in the book, and they couldn't hurt me.
有些东西 黑暗的东西
Some things, dark things.
光芒就像食物
The shining is like food.
俯瞰 它总是只是图片对我来说
The Overlook, it was always just pictures to me.
但我不像你那样发光
But I didn't shine like you.
没有人像你一样发光
Nobody shines like you.
所以你住在那该死的旅馆里
So you in that damn hotel,
你就像一百万瓦的电池 全部接通了电源
you were like a million watt battery, all plugged in.
它吃了它
And it ate it up.
世界是个饥饿的地方
World's a hungry place.
最黑暗的东西是饥饿的 他们会吃什么闪耀
And the darkest things are the hungriest, and they'll eat what shines.
像蚊子一样 像水痘一样涌来 对此无能为力
Swarm in, like mosquitoes, leeches. Can't do nothing about that.
您可以做什么
What you can do
是转向他们来反对他们
is turn what they come for against them.
我的祖父
My grandfather.
他是个贱人的儿子
He was a mean son of a bitch.
里面很黑和你爸爸一样的黑暗
Dark inside. Same type of dark as your dad.
打我毫无意义 我奶奶也 他死后我跳舞
Beat me senseless and my grandma too. And when he died I danced.
但他回来了
But he came home coming back.
站在我房间里
Standing in my room.
适合所有灰色和臭从任何模具生长在他身上的盒子
Suit all gray and stinking from whatever mold was growing on him in that box.
奶奶...
So, grandma...
她教我一个窍门
She taught me a trick.
给了我一个监狱
Gave me a prison.
我想让你知道这个盒子
I want you to know this box.
从内到外
Inside and out.
不要只是看它 触摸它
Don't just look at it, touch it.
把你的鼻子去 看看是否有气味
Stick your nose inside, see if there is a smell.
为什么？
Why?
因为你要建立一个就像在你的脑海里一样
Because you gonna build one just like it in your mind.
更特别的一个
One even more special.
下次那个婊子来了
So next time that bitch comes around.
你会准备好的
You'll be ready.
让我们把你带回妈妈家
Let's get you back to mama.
丹尼！
Danny!
你在这儿！
There you are!
你去哪里了？！
Where did you go?!
你把我吓死了半死
You scared me half to death.
你不要这样对我吗 你听到了吗？
Don't you do that to me, you hear?
别这样对我
Don't you ever do this to me.
Don't ever do this to me.
怎么了 医生？
What's up, Doc?
正在烹饪什么？
What's cooking?
是什么在做饭的小朋友？嗯 你是！
What's cooking little friend? Well, you are!
关键
Me?
是的
Yes.
哦 你杀了我！
Ouch, you are killing me!
你没事吧 医生？
You okay, Doc?
是的 妈妈 我没事
Yeah, Mom, I'm okay.
-你叫什么名字 可爱？ -丹
- What's your name again, cutie? - Dan.
丹
Dan.
你要吃那药
You gonna take that medicine.
加油 出去
Come on. Get out.
打 我想你杀了他
Shit, I think you killed him.
如果你杀了他呢？
What if you killed him?
我希望你杀了他
I hope you killed him.
你听到我说话了吗？
You hear me?
让我吻一下 它不会受伤
Let me kiss it won't hurt.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
哦不
No, no.
什么...
What a...
妈妈？
Mommy?
-妈妈？ -宝贝
- Mommy? - Baby.
在这里 这里
Here, here.
你可以把她的钱放回去 医生
You can put her money back, Doc.
你可以做这么多
You can do that much.
她拿走了我的
She took mine.
她可能买了一个可乐
She probably bought a coke with it.
医生！
Doc!
安 迪？
Andi?
没错
That's right.
你比你的照片更漂亮
You're prettier than your picture.
你比你老了
And you're older than yours.
我们留在这里 还是去什么地方？
We're staying here, or going somewhere?
你不想看电影吗？
Don't you wanna watch the movie?
我不明白有什么大惊小怪的
I don't see what the fuss is about.
聊天室浪漫 小女孩 没有意思
Chat-room romance, little girls, not interesting.
看着我 看看我是否答应了
Just watch, see if there's thing I promised.
最好是 因为她不是那种蒸汽
It better be, 'cause she's not all that steamy.
她去了
There she goes.
你不累吗？
Aren't you tired?
睡眠
Sleep.
好
Okay.
等 这是最好的部分
Wait. This is the best part.
我看着她做了3次 它永远不会变老
I watched her do it 3 times now, and it never gets old.
睡得更深 尽可能深
Sleep deeper. Deep as you can.
你感受到的痛苦只是一场梦
The pain you feel is only a dream.
当你妻子问的时候 你可以解释一个丢失的钱包
You can explain a lost wallet, when your wife asks.
但你不能解释吗？
But you can't explain this?
当你看着镜子时 你每天都会看到这个
This you'll see every day when you look in the mirror.
每次你看到它 你会大声说出来
And at every time you see it, you'll say out loud -
"我喜欢小女孩"
"I like little girls".
下次你去网上找个小女孩的时候
And the next time you go looking for a little girl online.
我要你记住
I want you to remember
那段时间你被一条响尾蛇咬了
that time you got bitten by a rattle snake.
这很有趣
That is interesting.
打扰一下 小姐？
Excuse me, Miss?
小姐？
Miss?
小姐 你在剧院里留下了些东西
Miss, you left something in the theater.
你想让我一个人呆着
You wanna leave me alone.
嗯 你好
Well, hi there.
你想让我走
You wanna let me go.
哦 没有甜心
Oh, no sweetie.
不 我没有
No, I don't.
妈妈 我为你做的 这是一张秘密卡
Mommy, I made this for you, it's a secret card.
谢谢你 阿杜
Thank you, Abadoo.
有人知道一个神奇的词吗？
Does anyone know a magic word?
你
You.
阿布拉卡达布拉
Abracadabra.
"阿布拉卡达布拉" 这是一个伟大的
"Abracadabra", that's a great one.
一个
One.
两
Two.
三
Three.
阿布拉卡达布拉！
Abracadabra!
我也知道魔法
I know magic too.
有时
Sometimes...
对不起
Sorry.
有人看见我的勺子了吗？
Has anyone seen my spoons?
我能做到
I can do that.
太好了 亲爱的
That's nice, sweetie.
-他们支持你！ -哦 他们支持我？
- They are on you! - Oh, they are on me?
管他呢？
What the hell?
戴夫
Dave.
阿布拉卡达布拉
Abracadabra.
哎呀
Oops.
哦 你好 有昏昏欲睡的头
Oh, hi there sleepy-head.
对不起
Sorry.
我不得不非常努力地让你睡觉
I had to sleep you pretty hard.
你很坚强
You are a tough one.
任性
Willful.
你知道我查过了
You know I checked.
3个月内有6个男人的脸颊上有小蛇咬纹身？
Six men in 3 months with those little snake bite tattoos on their cheeks?
我 你一直很忙
My, you've been busy.
蛇咬安迪 -你就是这个人
Snakebite Andi - that's who you are.
那么 我是谁？
So, who am I?
你是个疯狂的婊子 他绑架了我
You're some crazy bitch, who kidnapped me.
从现在开始的真相
Just the truth from now on.
你只会说真话
You will only speak the truth.
你是我见过的最漂亮的女人
You're the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
哦 我的上帝 工作得有点太好了 不是吗？
Oh my God, works a little too well, doesn't it?
这是交易蛇咬安迪
Here's the deal Snakebite Andi.
你是推手 嗯？你可以推人
You are pusher, hm? You can push people.
我们这有一阵子没在了
We haven't had a pusher around here for a little while.
所以 我要给你一笔交易 我已经近40年没有给过任何人了
So, I'm gonna offer you a deal I haven't offered anyone in almost 40 years.
你多大了 亲爱的？
How old are you, darling?
十五
Fifteen.
十五？
Fifteen?
哦 上帝 多么大的年龄啊
Oh, God, what an age.
你女人的春天 不是吗？
Springtime of your womanhood, isn't it?
你不再是女孩了 但你也没有一个凹痕
You are not a girl anymore but you don't have a single dent yet either.
重力甚至没注意到你
Gravity hasn't even noticed you.
不是15岁
Not in 15.
男人虽然...
Men though...
不不不 在没什么可耻的
No, no. no. No shame.
你付了钱 是吗？
You paid that back, didn't you?
这就是我给你的
That's what I'm offering you.
永远的春天
Springtime forever.
十年后 你还是15岁
Ten years from now you are still 15.
一百个？也许17岁
A hundred? Maybe 17.
吃得好
Eat well.
保持年轻 活得长
Stay young. Live long.
你喜欢吗？
You like it?
对不起 我只是...
Sorry I was just...
没关系 人们喜欢看它
That's okay, people love to look at it.
我们过去常在图书馆里设置这个
We used to set this up in the library.
社区项目只是独自夺走了生命
Community project just taken a life on its own.
我们从那儿的一个钟表城开始
We started with a clock town there.
-哦 是的 -只是不断成长
- Oh yeah. - Just keeps growing.
孩子们称它为"小城"
Kids call it "Tiny Town".
孩子们造的？
The kids built this?
有一些帮助 哦 是的
With some help, oh yeah.
保持下去 建了整个镇广场
Keep it up. Built the whole Town square.
你是下车还是骑在城镇附近？
Are you off the bus, or riding near town?
是的 公共汽车
Yeah, the bus.
在北方这样远的地方 坐公共汽车的人并不多
Not many ride bus this far North.
除非 他们正在寻找工作
Unless, they are looking for work.
是的
Yeah.
改变风景 或者...
Change of scenery, or...
你逃避了什么？
You're running away from something?
别介意我跳
Don't mind me hop on.
-新面孔 就这些 -是的
- New face, that's all. - Yeah.
所以我想 我离家出走
So I'm running away from myself, I guess.
逃离自己 那是一个泡菜
Running away from yourself, that is a pickle.
无论你走到哪里 你都带着自己
You take yourself with you wherever you go.
那不是婊子吗？
Isn't that the bitch?
租金为每周85美元 预付
Rent's $85 a week, payable upfront.
比利付了你的前两美元 休息给你
Billy paid your first two, rest's on you.
没有宠物没有派对无噪音
No pets. No parties. No noise.
我是一个安静的时间
I am a quiet time.
最后一个人也这么说
Last guy said the same.
数学学生
Math student.
甚至让他把墙上的黑板都画上去
Even let him paint the wall all blackboard,
这样他就可以在上面涂鸦他的小谜题了
so he could scribble his little puzzles up there.
不安静 不是这样
Wasn't quiet, no so.
他离开时连画都没涂上 但我很高兴我没有
Didn't even paint over this when he left. But I'm glad I didn't.
因为我可以为你带来一些简单
'Cause I can make this easy for you.
所以 你每天早上醒来都会看到它
So you see it every morning when you wake.
-你确定要为这小狗担保？ -很肯定
- You sure you wanna vouch for this pup? - Pretty sure.
这是你的 比利
It's your ass, Billy.
流血的心脏这一个
Bleeding heart this one.
我在楼下 一楼 如果你需要什么
I'm downstairs, ground floor, if you need anything.
明天找到我 我们再谈一些工作
Find me tomorrow, we'll talk about some work.
你为什么要这么做？
Why are you doing this?
你不了解我
You don't know me.
不 我没有
No I don't.
但我知道这个样 就像我说的
But I know the look, like I said.
有时候我...
And sometimes I...
得到这种对人的感觉 很难理解 我猜
get this feeling about people, hard to understand, I guess.
比你想象的要容易
Easier than you think.
-谢谢 -好吧
- Thanks. - All right.
准备好了吗？
You ready?
她准备好了
She's ready.
这些人是谁？
Who are these people?
之后你就会知道的
You'll find out after.
那边是格兰帕・弗利克 他会带领我们
Right over there is Grampa Flick, and he'll lead us.
躺下
Lie down.
那里
There.
无所畏惧 你明白吗？
No fear, you understand?
我们是真正的结 我们忍受
We are the True Knot, and we endure.
我们是被选中的
We are the chosen ones.
我们是幸运的
We are the fortunate ones.
什么被绑 不能解开
What is tied, cannot be untied.
这是一个女人
Here is a woman.
她会加入我们吗？
Would she join us?
她会把她的生活和我们的生活联系在一起吗？
Would she tie her life to our life?
是的
Yes.
说"是"
Say "yes".
是的
Yes.
这个很特别
This one's special.
她叫维奥莱特
Her name's Violet.
她剩下的不多了
There is not much of her left.
她尝到了
And she tastes
像花一样
like flowers.
深呼吸
Breathe deep.
在那里 拥抱它
There, embrace it.
拥抱它
Embrace it.
不！
No!
他们还没找到我们
They haven't found us yet.
他们习惯于听他哭
They were used to hearing him cry.
因为我把他一个人留了这么多
'Cause I left him alone for so much.
所以他们什么也没做
So they didn't do anything.
他们还没找到我们
And they haven't found us yet.
妈妈？
Mommy?
嘿
Hey.
你说你知道我的样子
You said that you knew my look.
你什么意思？
What did you mean?
你病了
You're sick.
你累了我能看到这么多
You're tired. I can see that much.
我需要帮助
I need help.
快进来 我们来谈谈
Come on in. We'll talk about it.
上帝 赐予我平静 接受我无法改变的事情
God, grant me the serenity to accept the things that I cannot change,
有勇气去改变我所能改变的事情
the courage to change the things that I can,
和智慧知道的区别
and the wisdom to know the difference.
鲍比今天过生日了
Bobby's got a big birthday today.
三年 三年清醒
Three years, three years sober.
谢谢 约翰
Thanks, John.
现在为房间里最重要的人
Now for the most important person in the room.
这里有新人吗？
Is anybody here a newbie?
有人有24小时？
Somebody's got 24 hours?
是的
Yeah.
新到城里了？
New to town, huh?
是的 我...
Yeah, I...
在那个房间里 我交付了一半的人 没有个人的东西
Nothing personal I delivered half of the people in that room.
-所以这是新面孔的一部分 就这些了 -这是丹・托伦斯
- So it's new faces part, that's all. - This is Dan Torrance.
他刚下车
He's fresh off the bus.
刚离开地面 看什么？
Fresh off the ground, by the look?
这里没有判断 兄弟
There's no judgment here, brother.
我是说 我们都去过那里 更糟糕的是 相信我
I mean, we've all been there, and worse, trust me.
哦 是的
Oh yeah.
如果你正在寻找一个翅膀爬下
If you are looking for a wing to climb under.
我不能说你在这里比比利・弗里曼做得更好
I can't say you do any better than Billy Freeman here.
谢谢你的盛情款待
Well, thank you for your hospitality.
我有点...
I'm a little...
我想我不习惯
I guess I'm not used to it.
你知道我们说什么
Well, you know what we say.
在你知道整个故事之前 你不能评判一个人
You can't judge someone till you know the whole story.
你可能认为你明白 但是...
You might think you understand, but...
-你没有 -你没有
- You don't. - You don't.
你今天好吗？
How are you today, all right?
我们的火车还在运行
Our train is still running.
很好听
That's good to hear.
你很好？
You good?
是的
Yeah.
-嗯 很好 丹 -是的
- Well, good to know you, Dan. - Yeah.
-再来一次 -谢谢
- Come again. - Thanks.
-希望不久能再见到你 -我会回来的
- Hope to see you again soon. - I'll come back, yeah.
真的好男人 他有天赋
Really good man, he's got a gift.
嘿 比利 等一下
Hey, Billy, hang on.
嘿 医生？
Hey, Doc?
你的手表
Your watch.
你丢了手表 你担心那个孩子...
You lost your watch, you were worried about the kid with...
左边 古彻斯
Gauche, Guchers...
什么？
What?
和古彻斯 或高彻斯 骨头的事情...
The kid with Guchers, or Gauchers, the bone thing...
-高彻病 -对
- Gaucher's disease. - Right.
你在医院浴室里洗手
You were washing your hands in the hospital bathroom and
你把它忘在肥皂分配器上了
you left it on the soap dispenser.
好吧 看看肥皂分配器
Well, just check on the soap dispenser.
-很高兴见到你 -是的
- It was good to meet you. - Yeah.
你怎么知道的？
How did you know?
我希望我能说
I wish I could say.
幸运的猜测
Lucky guess.
我的了
My ass.
直觉 我想 就像我内心的感觉 也许...
Intuition I suppose. Like a feeling in my gut, maybe...
一个幸运的猜测
A lucky guess.
你想在这里做什么？
What do you wanna do here?
你是什么意思？
What do you mean?
我是说在弗雷泽你为什么在这里？
I mean here in Frazier. Why are you here?
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
有些事和我一直做的不一样...
Something different than I've been doing...
更好的东西
Something better.
你去教堂？
You go to church?
这有关系吗？
Does it matter?
你相信某事吗
Do you believe in something, something
比你大？
bigger than you?
我们的信念不能使我们成为更好的人
Our beliefs don't make us better people.
我们的行动使我们成为更好的人
Our actions make us better people.
比利说你有条不紊的经验？
So Billy says you have orderly experience?
没错
That's right.
你现在在工作？
You're working right now?
在小镇上很少换班 帮助火车
Few shifts at Tiny Town, helping with the train.
因为我每周在里文顿之家疗养院做3天
'Cause I do 3 days a week at Rivington House hospice.
好有序是很难找到的
Good orderly is tough to find.
更难保持
Tougher to keep.
垂死的人打扰你吗？
Do dying people bother you?
不
No.
我们都快死了
We're all dying.
我们都是一个空气清新的大临终关怀中心
We're all just one big hospice with fresh air.
哦 你好
Oh, hi there.
你说没伤
You said it didn't hurt.
不是现在 是吗？
Doesn't now, does it?
感觉好像我快死了
It felt like I was dying.
我知道
I know.
你做到了
You did.
吃饭时你会感觉好些的
You'll feel better when you eat.
我还是人吗？
Am I still human?
你在乎吗？
Do you care?
嘿
Hey.
随它去
Let it be.
阿兹雷尔 离开他吧
Azrael, leave him be.
阿齐兹？
Azzie?
阿齐 来吧
Azzie, come on.
来吧 阿齐
Come on, Azzie.
医生？
Doc?
是你吗 医生？
Is that you, Doc?
不 我不是医生
No, I'm not a doctor.
你要我给你找个医生吗？
Do you want me to get you a doctor?
猫在我的床上
The cat's on my bed.
-哦 我会把她搬走 -没有
- Oh, I'll move her. - No.
我知道她会的
I knew she would be.
那只猫似乎总是知道
That cat always seems to know
当它的时间
when it's time.
我想是时候了
I guess it's time.
不 只是阿齐是个愚蠢的老猫
No, it's just Azzie being a silly old cat.
不
Nope.
自从我来到这里 就一直这样
Been that way ever since I got here.
猫知道
The cat knows
是时候睡觉了
when it's time to go to sleep.
大家都知道
Everybody knows that.
我要去.
I'm gonna die.
是的
Yes.
-让我给你找个人 -没有
- Let me get you someone. - No.
我知道它就要来了
I've known it was coming.
不会让它不那么可怕
Doesn't make it less scary.
是的
Yeah.
也许就像你说的
Maybe it's just like you say.
只是要睡觉了
Just going to sleep.
我是说没什么可怕的 只是睡着了
I mean there's nothing scary, it's just sleeping.
你是个奇怪的医生
You are a strange type of doctor.
我说过我不是医生
I told you I'm not a doctor.
我想你是
I think you are.
医生睡眠
Doctor Sleep.
医生 我很害怕会伤害或黑暗
Doc, I am so scared it's gonna hurt or be dark,
或什么都不是 我不想...
or be nothing at all, and I don't wanna...
没什么好害怕的
Nothing to be scared of.
只是要睡觉了
Just going to sleep.
最后 真正的 宁静的睡眠
Finally true, restful sleep.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你 医生
Thank you, doc.
听着 我不该在这里
Look, I shouldn't be here.
-让我来给你拿点... -不 不 不
- Let me go get you some... - No, no, no.
你正是你应该去的地方
You're exactly where you should be.
完全
Exactly.
我看见我妻子了
I see my wife.
丹 酒鬼
Dan, alcoholic.
嗨 丹
Hi, Dan.
我不太喜欢演讲
I'm not much of a speech guy.
只是想拿芯片
Just thought I'll hold the chip and
谈论什么弹出
talk about whatever popped up.
我在想我爸爸
I'm thinking about my dad.
他5岁时就去世了 所以我唯一了解他的方式
He died when I was 5, so the only way I got to know him,
我真的了解他是当我黑了
I really got to know him was when I went dark.
当我喝酒的时候
When I drank.
来使...
To dull the...
或
Or...
每当我想打破某人的脸
Whenever I wanted to break someone's face.
因为喝酒、发脾气和愤怒
'Cause the drinking and the temper and the anger.
我的东西是他的
Those things in me were his.
他们都是我所能认识的
And they were all I could know of him.
但现在.
But now.
嗯 现在我了解他有点不同 因为
Well, now I get to know him a little different, 'cause
他也站在这样的房间里一次
he also stood in a room like this once.
想为我好起来 我妈妈
Wanting to get well for me, my mom.
他手里拿着一块芯片 芯片说"5个月"
And he has a chip in his hand, and chip said "5 months".
那天他...
And on that day he...
在一切之前
Before it all.
那一天 他只想站在我现在的站位上
Well, on that day all he wanted in the world was to stand where I'm standing now.
我在这里 所以...
And here I am, so...
所以 谢谢你 我们两个 我想
So, thank you for us both, I guess.
这是给杰克・托伦斯的
This is for Jack Torrance.
嘿 查理
Hey, Charlie.
医生？
Doc?
我想我不需要问你为什么这个小时在这里
Guess I don't need to ask why you are here this hour.
你痛吗？
You have pain?
你要我让克劳德特给你带个药丸吗？
Do you want me to get Claudette to bring you a pill?
药丸并不重要
Pill won't matter.
我不怕地狱 医生
I'm not scared of Hell, Doc.
我过着体面的生活
I lived a decent life.
无论如何 不要以为有这样一个地方
Don't think there is such a place anyway.
我想我很害怕
I guess I'm scared
什么都没有
there's nothing.
我们不会结束的 查理
We don't end, Charlie.
我知道这一点是肯定的
I know that for certain.
我不太知道 但是
I don't know much else, but
我知道我们不会结束
I know that we don't end.
蓝 莓
Blueberries.
我能尝到我妈妈以前种植的蓝莓
I can taste blueberries my mother used to grow.
你能尝尝吗？
Can you taste them?
是的 我可以
Yeah, I can.
我可以通过收音机听到弗兰克的声音
And I can hear Frank over radio.
以前 工具旁边有一个新的工作台
One used to have a new work bench next to your tools.
跟我飞吧
Come fly with me
让我们飞吧 我们飞走了
Let's fly, let's fly away
如果你能用一些异国情调的酒
If you can use some exotic booze
远孟买有一家酒吧
There's a bar in far Bombay
跟我飞吧
Come fly with me
让我们飞翔 让我们飞翔
Let's fly, let's fly
离开
Away
一会儿 小笔友
In a minute, little pen pal.
阿布拉 学校
Abra, school.
好吧 我知道
Fine, I know.
嘿 葛兰 你见过罗西吗？
Hey gramps, have you seen Rosie?
t望 塔
Watchtower.
你感觉还好吗？
You feeling okay?
桃子好
Peach okay.
嘿
Hey.
对不起 打扰一下
Sorry to interrupt.
运气好吗？
Any luck?
越来越近了
Getting closer.
我想他在爱荷华州的某个地方
He's somewhere in Iowa, I think.
一旦我确定他找到了 我们都会走一次很长的路程
We'll all take a nice long road trip once I'm sure I found him.
但直到我...
But until I do...
你得打开毒气罐 罗西
You gotta open the canister, Rosie.
我们6个月前就拿了蒸汽 乌鸦 6个月什么都不是
We took steam 6 months ago, Crow, 6 months is nothing.
特拉华州的那个孩子没有那么有蒸汽 而且已经出现了
That kid in Delaware wasn't so steamy and it's already showing.
-你看到弗利克爷爷的头发了吗？ -是的
- You see Grandpa Flick's hair, yeah? - Yeah.
我认为他不好
I don't think he's well.
自从尼克松执政以来 弗利克爷爷一直不太好
Grandpa Flick hasn't been well since Nixon was in office.
我知道 但是...
I know, but...
我们需要吃饭 我们所有人
We need to eat, all of us.
还是罐子太低了？
Or the canisters just low?
当然不是
Of course not.
只是没有必要浪费一个 如果你接近一个杀人
Just no need to waste one if you are close to a kill.
罗西
Rosie.
我可能需要它只是为了找到他
I might need it just to find him.
我们过去更蒸汽
We used to be more steamy.
别傻了 来吧
Don't be daft, come on.
这就像根说:
That's like a root say:
在50年我成长 人们过去更邻里
in 50 years I grow, people used to be more neighborly.
但这是真的 罗西
But it's true, Rosie.
那里蒸汽少了 也变弱了
There's less steam out there and it's weaker too.
不知道是他们的手机 饮食或Netflix或什么
Don't know if it's their cell phones, or diets or Netflix or what,
但这些天我没有任何意义
but I am not picking up any sense these days,
一旦我这么做 罗西 他们只是...
and once that I do, Rosie, they are just...
今晚我会把罐子打开 把大家紧闭起来
I'll open the canister tonight to tight everyone up.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你知道吗 罗西？ -我知道吗？
- You know what, Rosie? - I know what?
这就是为什么你每天都在这里
It's why you up here every day.
这就是为什么你总是在这里 不管你告诉别人什么
It's why you are always up here, no matter what you tell the others.
世界并不太如蒸汽 你正在寻找鲸鱼
The world's not as steamy, and you are looking for a whale.
看这个孩子19号
Watch this kid. Number 19.
那孩子很自然
That kid is a natural.
他每次都击球
He hits the ball every time.
就像他能读出投手的思想一样
Like he can read the pitcher's mind.
是吗？
Is that right?
看 你看
See, you watch.
这些天之一 这些天才球探之一
One of these days one of those talent scouts
会把胜利给布莱德那里 你看
is gonna give win to Brad there, you watch.
嘿 19岁
Hey, 19.
刚刚看了你的游戏
Just saw your game.
你准备好参加专业了
You are ready for the majors.
-玩得很好 -谢谢
- Well played. - Thanks.
嘿 你要回家了？
Hey, you're heading home?
你想跳进去 我送你一程
You wanna hop in, I'll give you a ride.
不 非常接近
No, it's real close.
我很好
I'm good.
没关系
It's okay.
我们是朋友 你想跳进去 我们带你回家吧
We're friends, you wanna hop in. We'll take you right home.
你可以带我回家
You can take me right home.
你相信我
You trust me.
我相信你
I trust you.
不 不 求你了！
No, no please!
不！请让我走！
No! Please let me go!
请我不会告诉 请！
Please I won't tell, please!
19号
Number 19.
孩子 你很好
Kid you were good.
不！
No!
不 请让我走！
No, please let me go!
我不会说 我不会说！请！
I won't tell, I won't tell! Please!
没关系
It's okay.
请
Please.
你要伤害我吗？
Are you gonna hurt me?
是的
Yes.
不！
No!
疼痛净化蒸汽
Pain purifies steam.
恐惧也 所以 你明白
Fear too, so, you understand.
停止
Stop.
停止！
Stop!
停下 怪物！
Stop, monster!
停下 停下
Stop, stop.
谁？
Who is it?
停下 停下！
Stop, stop!
打开！
Abra!
哦不！
No, no!
停下！
Stop it!
-阿布拉 -停下！
- Abra. - Stop it!
耶稣
Jesus.
好
Okay.
好了 准备好了吗？
Okay, ready?
他们杀了他
They killed him.
-没事的 -没事的
- It's okay. - It's all right.
我们有个看者
We had a looker.
今晚？
Tonight?
是的
Yeah.
大蒸汽？
Big steam?
哦 亲爱的 它很大
Oh, honey, it was huge.
哪里？
Where?
我想是东海岸
East Coast, I think.
你是说有人从1500英里外看的？
You are saying someone looked in from 1500 miles away?
也许再远一点
Maybe farther.
男孩还是女孩？
Boy or girl?
女孩 我想
Girl, I think.
她这么快就出去了
She was out of there so fast.
但我发誓 乌鸦爸爸
But I swear, Crow Daddy.
我没有感觉到那样的力量
I haven't felt power like that.
原始的力量 在这么久
Raw power like that in so long.
我们需要调查一下吗？
Do we need to look into it?
越快越好
Sooner the better.
孩子的父母吓坏了
Kid's parents freak out.
送她去看精神病医生
Send her to a psychiatrist.
他们给她吃药可能会毁了蒸汽
And they get her on pills. Could ruin the steam.
不 回馈 所以这个孩子就像
No, giving back, so this kid it's like
把一块萨兰包裹在探照灯上
turning a piece of saran wrap over searchlight.
我不知道她在哪儿
I don't know where she is.
但是当她回来的时候 她会回来的
But when she comes back, and she'll be back.
哦 我会准备好的 亲爱的
Oh, I'll be ready, honey.
我会准备好的
I'll be ready.
早上
Morning.
猜猜怎么着？
Guess what?
我交了个新朋友
I made a new friend.
他的名字叫丹
His name is Dan.
艾伯斯 你没事吧？
Abbs, are you okay?
昨晚 我...
Last night, I...
我没事
I'm okay.
很抱歉
Sorry about that.
我知道你的头有时就像收音机
I know that head of yours is like a radio sometimes.
你拿起一些奇怪的车站
And you pick up some weird stations.
没有什么奇怪的
Nothing weird like that.
不再是了
Not anymore.
好吧
All right...
我得学习 如果我不学习...
I gotta study, if I don't study...
跑步的地方 交给11 然后...
Running place, hand off to 11, and...
如果我...
Coach is gonna kill me if I'm...
为什么他不喜欢我？
Why doesn't he like me?
我的头发？我应该换发型吗？
My hair? Should I change my haircut?
怪物又盯着我看
The freak is staring at me again.
她在看什么？
What is she staring at?
怪物
Freak.
-嘿 阿多 -嘿 爸爸
- Hey, Abadoo. - Hey, dad.
学校还好吗？
Is school okay?
书怎么样？
How is the book?
好
Good.
是的 很好
Yeah, going good.
我在写查尔斯顿和黑底
I'm writing about Charleston and Black Bottom.
你知道...
And it's, you know like...
我要开始作业
I'm going to start my homework.
好 好
Okay. Good.
很好 亲爱的
That's good, sweetie.
想想哈佛在3年
Think Harvard in 3 years.
-会看的 -是的 我们拭了
- Will see - Yeah, we will see.
嗯 你好
Well, hi there.
出去！
Get out!
出去！滚出我的头！
Get out! Get out off my head!
出去！
Get out!
-夫人 你没事吧？ -不！不要！
- Ma'am, are you okay? - No! Don't!
是的 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
我很好
I'm fine.
耶稣
Jesus.
丹？
Dan?
起床
Get up.
来吧 丹
Come on, Dan.
-发生什么事了？ -你刚掉下去了
- What happened? - You just dropped.
我以为你中风了
I thought you were having a stroke.
谁是托尼？
Who's Tony?
什么？
What?
你一直说"请帮帮我 托尼"
You kept saying "Please help me, Tony".
对此我很抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
罗西？
Rosie?
我们有麻烦了
We've got a problem.
-跟我说话 -看者
- Talk to me. - The looker.
是的 她又找到我了
Yeah, she found me again.
如何？
How?
我不知道 我不在乎
I don't know, I don't care.
我们必须拥有她 克劳我们必须这样做！
We have to have her, Crow. We have to!
她知道你是谁吗？我们在哪里？
Does she know who you are? Where we are?
不 我不知道 我不知道 我不认为 那不重要 看...
No. I don't know, I don't, I don't think. That's not the important, look...
我说她很有蒸汽 对吧？
I said she's huge steam, right?
是的 它甚至比那还要大
Yeah, it's even bigger than that.
我试着背弃她
I tried to turn around on her
她把我从她身上吹出来 就像我什么都不是一样
and she blew me out of her like I was nothing.
-废话 -不 我从未遇到过
- Bullshit. - No, never happened to me, ever.
我会说那是不可能的
I would've said that was impossible.
她是食物还是我们把她转过来？
Is she food or do we turn her?
我们不把她转过来
We don't turn her.
罗西 你确定吗？
Rosie, are you sure?
如果她是你所说的...
If she's what you say she is...
那我们不想要任何比我们更有能力的人
Then we don't want anyone with that power than us.
耶兹 想想看
Jeez, think about it.
有美好的一天
Have a great day.
你也是
You too.
你好
Hi.
比利
Billy.
你能听到我说话吗？
You can hear me?
让我们用我们外面的声音 好吗？
Let's use our outside voices, all right?
你找到我了？
You tracked me down?
比我想象的要容易
It was easier than I thought.
比如 GPS 但在我的脑海里
Like, GPS, but in my head.
听着 我不是说任何冒犯 但
Look, I don't mean any offense, but
现在和现在 一个成长中的男人和一个十几岁的女孩坐在公园的长椅上...
this day and age, a grow man sitting with a teenage girl on a park bench...
我是艾布拉・斯通 如果有人问 你是我的叔叔
I'm Abra Stone, and if anyone asks - you are my uncle.
丹叔叔
Uncle Dan.
这甚至不是谎言 不是完全的
And that's not even a lie, not totally.
你魔法 像我一样
You magic, like me.
我不知道魔法
I don't know about magic.
我一直称它为"闪亮的"
I've always called it "the shining".
是的 我们都闪耀
And yeah, we both shine.
你父母知道吗？
Do your parents know?
关于我的光芒？
About my shine?
他们不谈论它
They don't talk about it.
或者 如果我使用它 他们看我不同
Or if I use it, they look at me different.
当我还是个孩子的时候 我不懂那光芒
When I was a kid I didn't understand the shining.
我叫它"托尼"
I called it "Tony".
以为那是我想象中的朋友
Thought it was my imaginary friend.
我以为你是我想象中的朋友
I thought you were my imaginary friend
很长一段时间
for a long time.
我们有多少人在那里？
How many of us are out there?
有很多人有一点点的光芒
There are a lot of people who have a little bit of shine,
他们甚至不知道
they don't even know it.
他们似乎总是带着花回家 当他们的妻子伤心时
They always seem to come home with flowers when their wives are sad,
或者他们在学校考试中表现很好 他们没有学习
or they do well in the school test they didn't study for.
但我一生只见过两三个人 他们知道他们闪闪发光
But I only met 2 or 3 people in my whole life who knew they shined.
那个棒球男孩闪闪发光
The baseball boy shined.
他的名字是布拉德利・特雷弗
His name was Bradley Trevor.
这些人
These people.
他们看起来像人反正 他们带走了他
They look like people anyway, they took him
他们吃了他
And they ate him.
他们吃了他的光芒
They ate his shine.
你能感觉到吗？
You could feel it?
他能感觉到我
And he could feel me.
如果你能得到他的东西
If you could get something of his.
如果你能去爱荷华州
If you could go to Iowa.
-不 等等... -我可以帮你找到他
- No, hang on... - I can help you find him.
这样他的父母就会知道他在哪里
That way his parents would know where he was.
他们至少可以把他埋起来
They could bury him right at least.
我们也可以拿他的手套
We could also get his glove.
-如果我能触摸手套 我可以追踪他们 -简单 简单
- If I can touch that glove I can track them. - Easy, easy.
因为巴里是块 我想那是他的名字
Because Barry the Chunk, I think that was his name.
有一段时间 在他们杀了他之前
For a while, before they killed him.
他戴着它
He was wearing it.
阿布拉 回家吧
Abra, go home.
别追这些人
Don't chase these people.
不要加重他们
Don't aggravate them.
无论你做什么 都不要吸引他们的注意
Whatever you do, don't attract their attention.
找点东西 什么
Find something, anything.
嗯 几乎任何阻止你的光芒
Well, almost anything to stop that shine of yours.
保持低头 希望上帝 这些人
Keep your head down and hope to God that these people
和他们一样的东西 他们...
and anything like them that they...
他们没看见你
That they don't see you.
如果他们看到你 他们会回来
If they see you they come back.
阿布拉 你听到我说话了吗？
Abra, do you hear me?
他们回来了
They come back.
低着头 保持安全
Keep your head down, stay safe.
对不起
I'm sorry.
嘿 阿齐
Hey, Azzie.
你今晚的电线被划掉了
You got your wires crossed tonight.
那个房间是空的 阿齐
That room's empty, Azzie.
那个房间里没人
There's no one in that room.
坚持住 医生
Hang on, Doc.
迪克？
Dick?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
-我以为是... -我以为我是从俯瞰的
- I thought it was... - Thought I was from the Overlook.
差点把我关起来
Almost locked me up.
还在从他们那里得到生意？老鬼？
Still getting business from them old ghosts?
不 不是好几年了
No, not for years.
霍勒斯・德温特是最后一个 他西装上的纸屑
Horace Derwent was the last one, confetti on his suit.
说:"伟大的党 不是吗？
Said: "Great party, isn't it?"
打 他脸上的笑容 直到我掏出盒子给他
Shit, he did a grin on his face till I pulled out box for him.
那笑容就快了
That grin went fast.
那时我从没想过要问你
It never occurred me to ask you back then.
那些箱子里会发生什么事？
What happens to them in those boxes?
他们死在那里吗？
Do they die in there?
你在乎吗？
Do you care?
我想你
I missed you.
已经很久了？
Has it been a long time?
说不出来
Can't tell.
这个世界对我来说是一个梦想
This world is a dream of a dream to me now.
八年了 再多一点
Eight years, little more.
你为什么在这里？
Why are you here?
我来这里是因为它一切都来了
I'm here because it all comes round.
卡是个轮子 医生
Ka is a wheel, Doc.
如果这些空魔鬼在你是坦克时找到你
If these empty devils ever found you when you were a tank.
如果他们嗅到你
If they'd even sniffed you
你会死很久了
you'd be long dead.
他们吃尖叫和喝痛
They eat screams and drink pain.
他们注意到了那个小女孩
And they've noticed that little girl.
他们可能会杀了她
They might kill her.
可能会把她
Might turn her.
或者可能留着她 直到她都用不着 那可是最糟糕的
Or might keep her, till she's all used up and that'd be worst of all.
你不能让他们
You can't let them.
为什么是我？
Why me?
因为她找到你了
Because she found you.
因为她出现了见鬼 医生 为什么是我？
Because she showed up. Hell, Doc, why me?
有一天你刚走进我的厨房 我还是被钩住了
You just rocked on into my kitchen one day and I'm still on the hook.
我到底要怎么做？
What the hell am I supposed to do?
给她买她要求的
Get her what she asked for.
你不会再见我了 医生
You won't see me again, Doc.
这是我最后的梦
This is my last dream.
在我看来 你长大了很好 儿子
It seems to me you grew up fine, son.
但你还是欠了一笔债
But you still owe a debt.
付钱吧
Pay it.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 妈妈
Hey, Mom.
你没事吧？
You're feeling okay?
晚餐时我们想念你
We missed you at dinner.
我很好 只是度过了艰难的一天
I'm okay, just had a rough day.
我早上要飞出去看MoMo
I'm flying out to see MoMo in the morning.
我会尽快回来的
I'll be back as soon as I can.
艾伯斯 她...
Abbs, does she...
她这次会挺过难关的？
She's gonna pull through this time?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我希望如此
But I hope so.
告诉她我爱她
Tell her I love her.
继续睡觉 公主
Keep sleeping, princess.
你坐炉
You hobs.
你花了一生的时间 做小盒子
You spend your whole lives, making little boxes.
小小的回忆
Little memories.
你认为他们让你这么富有？
You think they make you so rich?
你应该看看我的 孩子
You should see mine, kiddo.
我的头脑是一座大教堂
My mind's a cathedral.
嗯 你好
Well, hi there.
他说你会回来的
He said you'd come back.
而你做到了
And you did.
好
Good.
回去 回来！
Get back, get back!
你只是个该死的孩子
You are just a fucking child.
你在哪里？
Where did you?
哪里...
Where...
你去哪里了？
Where did you go?
你在哪里...
Where did you...
不
No.
出去！出去！
Get out! Get out!
出去！
Get out!
玫瑰？
Rose?
陷阱
Trap.
陷阱！
Trap!
到底发生什么事了？
What the hell happened?
-小婊子为我设了个陷阱 -哦 你的手
- Little bitch set a trap for me. - Oh, your hand.
罗斯 冷静点冷静
Rose, calm down. Calm down.
我们知道她现在在哪 对吧？现在我们知道了
We know where she is now, right? Now we know.
她在我的脑子里
She was in my head.
-什么？ -偷盗
- What? - Stealing.
-她知道什么？ -我不知道 我不知道
- What does she know? - I don't know, I don't know.
-她看到了多少？ -我不知道！
- How much did she see? - I don't know!
有问题
There's a problem.
不是现在！
Not now!
爷爷弗利克
Grandpa Flick.
我想他在骑自行车
I think he's cycling.
丹叔叔 丹叔叔！
Uncle Dan, Uncle Dan!
我伤害了她我真的伤害了她
I hurt her. I really hurt her.
我伤害了她 她应得的 但这不是最好的部分
I hurt her, and she deserved it, but that's not the best part.
最好的部分是 我得到了她的头
The best part is I got in her head.
我在她的脑袋里
I got in her head.
-丹叔叔？ -哦 上帝 阿布拉
- Uncle Dan? - Oh, God, Abra.
你都干了些什么？
What have you done?
和孩子谈谈
Just talk to the kid.
如果我们要这样做 那么让我们这样做
If we gonna do this, then let's do this.
嗨 阿布拉
Hi, Abra.
我能听到你说话
I can hear you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你会的
You will.
我以为我们会永远活着
I thought we'll live forever.
有人答应过你吗 安蒂？
Did someone promise you that, Andi?
有人说你是不朽的吗？
Did someone say you're immortal?
我说:"活得长 吃得好"
I said: "live long, eat well".
我们可以活得长 活得长
We can live long, very long.
我们做 我们大多数人
And we do, most of us.
但是我们吃得不好
But we haven't been eating well.
很久没有了
Not for a long time.
罗西 他走了
Rosie, he's going.
罗西
Rosie.
是的 爱？
Yes, love?
-我很害怕 -不 不是
- I am scared. - No, you are not.
你看着帝国兴衰
You watched empires rise and fall.
在罗马的角斗士们欢呼雀跃
Cheered the gladiators in Rome.
横渡海洋到新世界
Sailed across oceans to new worlds.
靠国王、王子和教皇
Fed on kings and princes, and popes.
他们写了你的神话
They wrote myths of you.
并制作了雕像
And made statues.
他们在村庄、床和摩天大楼里颤抖
And they trembled in their villages and beds and skyscrapers.
所以没有
So no.
你不害怕
You are not scared.
你是个国王
You're a king.
你吃恐惧
And you eat fear.
嘿 兄弟
Hey, bro.
凌晨4点
It's 4 AM.
你总是看见我 比利
You've always seen me Billy.
你对人很有感觉 这么说公平吗？
You have a good sense about people, is that fair to say?
是的 但为什么？
Yeah, but why?
你以为我是个诚实的人 一个好人？
You think I'm an honest man, a good man?
是的 是的 丹
I do, I do, Dan.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
但我首先需要你听一个故事
But first thing I need is for you to listen to a story
比你试图相信我更努力
and try harder than you've ever tried to believe me.
事情进行的怎么样了？
How is it going?
嗨 你不该准备上学吗？
Hi, shouldn't you be getting ready for school?
是的 但是我想跟着
Yeah, but I wanted to tag along.
你开了多久了？
How long have you been driving?
几个小时左右
For few hours or so.
我们今晚应该晚到
We should get there tonight late.
那是谁？
Who's that?
那是我的朋友
That's my friend.
也许我最好的朋友
Maybe my best friend.
你应该看到她的脸
You should've seen her face.
她很害怕 丹叔叔
She was scared, Uncle Dan.
像所有的孩子一样害怕
Scared like all those kids were scared.
她杀的那些孩子
All those kids she's killed.
她太生气了 太害怕了 我都上不去
She was so mad and so scared that I got in.
那是个新把戏
That was a new trick.
我以前从没做过
I've never done that before.
是的 我也不是 感觉怎么样？
Yeah, me neither. What was it like?
就像图书馆一样
Like a library.
我想我们都是里面的图书馆
I guess we're all libraries inside.
你干的是谁干的？
Who did you do it?
像这样 只是一点点推
Like this, just a little push.
打开！
Abra!
对不起 对不起
Sorry, sorry.
-对不起 我不是故意的 -没事的
- I'm sorry, I didn't mean to. - It's okay.
那些箱子是什么？
What were all those boxes?
什么
Nothing.
骗子
Liar.
当我还是个孩子的时候
When I was a kid,
比你小 我碰到了类似这些东西的东西
younger than you I bumped into something like these things,
像他们一样吃了
that ate like they do.
但它不是一个人 而是一个地方
But it wasn't a person, it was a place.
他们关闭了它后 让它腐烂
They closed it downafter and let it rot.
但是那些住在那里的东西...
But the things that lived there, these...
别再去那里闲逛了
Don't go poking around there again.
好 我不会的 我保证
Okay. I won't, I promise.
我们差不多准备好了 我们只是 装载
We are almost ready, we are just, loading up.
好
Good.
我们在路上把车队弄到了 一两天后就把她弄到了
We got the caravan on the road, and we'll have her in a day or two.
我认为你不应该来 罗西
I don't think you should come, Rosie.
你刚才说的是什么？
The fuck did you just say?
她攻击了你 她在你的脑袋里
She attacked you, she got in your head.
是的 不会再发生了
Yeah, it won't happen again.
谁知道在你把她踢出去之前她得到了多少？
And who knows how much she got to before you kicked her out?
她是我的 克劳
She's mine, Crow.
现在 据我们所知 你是我们中唯一她能追踪的人
Right now as far as we know you are the only of us she could track.
现在 她看到你来了...
Now, she sees you coming...
她能跑
She could run,
或设置另一个陷阱
or set another trap.
你知道我是对的
You know I'm right about this.
如果她捉弄你
If she pulls a trick on you.
-是吗？ -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
但我有我自己的一些技巧
But I got some tricks on my own.
是的 我想我们在这里
Yeah, I think we're here.
好
Okay.
看看我能否抓住她
Will see if I can get her.
打开？
Abra?
那是标志
That's the sign.
退后一下
Pull around back.
她说要退后一把
She says to pull around back.
-我会告诉你什么时候停下来 -她会告诉我们什么时候停下来
- And I'll tell you when to stop. - She'll tell us when to stop.
我该怎么告诉你 我不知道
How do I tell you, I don't know.
我不知道我希望你是正确还是错误
I don't know whether I hope you're right or wrong about this.
我是说如果你错了 我的朋友是疯了
I mean if you are wrong - my friend is crazy.
我的意思是全面
I mean full-blown
心理崩溃假想怪物杀死假想的孩子
mental breakdown imaginary monsters killing imaginary kids
疯狂
bonkers.
但是 你知道的 我可以这样做
But, you know. I can work with that.
-如果你是对的 -我知道
- If you're right though. - I know.
更糟
So much worse.
你应该回家
You should go home.
什么？
What?
不 不是你
No, not you.
我能处理
I can handle it.
不
No.
我们从这里开始
We'll take it from here.
好吧 只有我们
Okay, it's just us.
你闻到了吗？
You smell that?
我过去常打猎 我跟你说过吗？
I used to hunt, did I ever tell you that?
不
No.
鹿
Deer.
这个夏天
This one summer.
我点击了这个降压
I clicked this buck.
我跟踪他2天
I was tracking him for 2 days.
我中枪了
I got the shot.
他点击他 他跑掉了 我走了
Clicked him, he ran off, I went after.
想一下 他不会持续太久的
Figured, he wasn't gonna last long.
他消失了
And he vanished.
打开 蒸发
Just open, evaporated.
没有痕迹 真的令人费解
Without a trace, truly baffling.
五天后
Five days later.
我在尝试一个在数英里之外的地方
I'm trying a different spot, miles away.
我四处寻找盲人的点
I come around, looking for a spot for the blind.
然后我闻到了他
Then I smelled him.
闻到他的味道
Smelled him.
找到了那块钱
Found that buck.
托起一个空心的树干
Held up to a hollow trunk.
死了几天
Dead for days.
气味
The smell.
从那以后 一天也没打猎过
Never hunted a day since.
这是同样的气味
This is the same smell.
比利
Billy.
哦 我的上帝！
Oh, my God!
搞什么？
What the fuck?
他妈的
Fuck.
妈的 丹尼尔！搞什么？！
Fuck, Daniel! What the fuck?!
他们甚至没有深深地埋葬他 他们把他埋在浅层
They didn't even bury him deeply. They buried him shallow.
对不起 比利
I'm sorry, Billy.
你让我们进入什么？
What did you get us into?
做那的人
The people who did that.
他们不是人
They are not people.
不 不 他们不是
No, no they ain't.
谁愿意对一个小男孩那样做
Who would wanna do that to a little boy.
他们不是人
They ain't people.
你拿到了吗？
Did you get it?
是的 我们拿到了
Yeah, we got it.
她回来了吗？
Is she back?
我们要回到你家我们早上回来
We're heading back to you. We'll be back in the morning.
我们停下来了
We got a stop to make.
我需要你告诉你的父母发生了什么事
I need you to show your parents what's happening.
不
No.
-是的 -没有
- Yeah. - No.
他们几乎认为我很正常
They almost think I'm normal.
如果我告诉他们 他们会...
If I tell them, they'll...
罗斯会通过他们来接近你
Rose will go through them to get to you.
你知道的 不是吗？
You know that, don't you?
她不用再三考虑就把它们砍下来
She'll cut them down without a second thought.
她来了 阿布拉
And she's coming, Abra.
他们需要知道
They need to know.
那我们要阻止什么？
So what's the stop we gotta make?
你还有那些老鹿步枪吗？
You still got those old deer rifles?
你是丹叔叔？
You Uncle Dan?
-你以为你是谁？ -先生
- Who the fuck do you think you are? - Sir.
她13岁了
She's 13 years old.
阿布拉 我让你给他看
Abra, I told you to show him.
-我告诉他了 -不一样
- I told him. - That's not the same.
我要在叫警察之前踢你的屁股 嗯？
I'm gonna kick your ass before I call the police, huh?
-嘿 -不 不 开门
- Hey. - No, no, Abra.
别说她的名字！
Don't you say her name!
打开
Abra.
对不起 斯通先生 我是朋友
I'm sorry, Mr. Stone, I am a friend.
她告诉你的一切都是真的
Everything she told you is true.
-不 谢谢 -没有
- No thanks. - No.
那些人
Those people.
他们知道我女儿的事吗？
They know about my daughter?
他们有
They do.
他们迟早会来的
And sooner or later they're coming.
我得做点什么
I gotta do something.
我会打电话给警察 联邦调查局
I will call the police, the FBI.
那些人在身边已经很久了 先生
Those people have been around a long long time, sir.
他们很富有 有联系
They're rich, connected.
我不认为他们担心警察
I don't think they're worried about the police.
他们在哪？
Where are they?
他们什么时候来？我们能去哪里？
When are they coming? Where can we go?
阿布拉可以回答这个问题
Abra can answer that.
如果她准备好了
If she's ready.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
你确定要这么做吗？
You sure you wanna do this?
我必须.
I have to.
I-95.
巴里 乌鸦 蛇和其他几个人
Barry, the Crow, the Snake and a few others.
树没那么变...
The trees haven't changed that much so...
也许马萨诸塞州 但是...
Maybe Massachusetts, but...
-他们很接近 -罗斯？
- They are close. - Rose?
没看见她
Didn't see her.
但他们来了
But they're coming.
这是她唯一看到的房间？
This is the only room she saw?
没错
That's right.
我做了一些改变 藏了几样东西
And I made a few changes. Hid a few things.
好吧
All right.
他们会试着追踪你
Well, they'll be trying to track you.
试着抓住
Try to catch on.
你会让他们
And you gonna let them.
你疯了吗？
Are you crazy?
可能吧 但你要让他们
Possibly, but you gonna let them.
然后我需要你尝试一下小把戏
And then I need you to try and do a little trick.
魔术？
A magic trick?
他们在跟踪我们
They're following us.
集中注意力 你得保持下去 直到他们降落
Concentrate, you gotta keep it up until they land.
我知道
I know.
这应该工作
This should work.
好的百叶窗一遍又一遍
Good blinds over and there.
他们还在附近？
They still close?
越来越近了 我想
Getting closer, I think.
这太难了
This is tough.
我知道 我知道 还要多久？
I know, I know, how much longer?
好的 乌鸦爸爸
Okay, Crow Daddy.
去找她
Go get her.
你看起来很放松
You look relaxed.
你感觉很放松 不是吗 阿布拉？
You feel relaxed, don't you, Abra?
我想
I guess.
你应该.
You should.
放松
Just relax.
我们是朋友
We're friends.
你们是朋友
You're friends.
没错
That's right.
只是朋友
Just friends.
我们想带你去见更多的朋友
And we wanna take you to meet more friends.
好朋友
Good friends.
该死
Oh, shit.
他们跟你说话的方式
They way they talked you up,
我想的可能比那更困难一点
I was thinking maybe a little harder than that.
搞什么？
What the fuck?
帕勒技巧 只是该死的客厅把戏！
Parlor tricks, just fucking parlor tricks!
不！滚出去！
No! Get out of there!
滚出去！
Get out of there!
不！
No!
这是你应得的
You deserve it.
你们都配得上它
You deserve it, all of you.
不！
No!
他妈的
Fuck.
停止
Stop.
我只有个问题要告诉你 亲爱的
I just got one question for you, sweetie.
你不困吗？
Aren't you sleepy?
你很困
You're sleepy.
睡眠
Sleep.
睡眠！
Sleep!
醒醒 丹叔叔！
Wake up, Uncle Dan!
醒来！
Wake up!
该死的男人
Fucking men.
退后 比利
Stay back, Billy.
自杀吧
Kill yourself.
不
No.
比利！
Billy!
有一个失踪了
There is one missing.
我没看见乌鸦 乌鸦在哪里？
I didn't see the Crow, where is the Crow?
你好 阿布拉
Hello, Abra.
打开！
Abra!
很好 你醒了
Good, you're awake.
丹
Dan.
别麻烦了
Don't bother.
我怎么了？
What's wrong with me?
你被人了 米西
You've been dosed, Missy.
比我以前用过的都多
More than I've ever used before.
我让你在这里和那里醒来 但
I let you wake up here and there, but
你的蒸汽很快就睡着了
that steam of yours is fast asleep.
我爸爸
My dad.
我爸爸怎么了？
What happened to my dad?
今天有很多好人被杀了
A lot of good people killed today.
很多好人
A lot of good people.
我很愿意告诉你有人会付钱的
I'd love to tell you someone will pay.
某种正义 雨下今天的悲惨事件 但
Some kind of justice, raining down on the sad events today, but
不是那样工作的
doesn't work like that.
我们总会有你
We were always gonna have you.
我的一些人死了
Some of my people are dead.
你的一些已经死了
Some of yours are dead.
结果没有改变
Outcome didn't change still.
想想看
Think on that a minute.
结果没有改变
The outcome didn't change,
所以他们的死
so their deaths,
所有
all of them -
只是浪费
just a waste.
你带给我们所有人的浪费 小姐
The waste you brought on to us all, young lady.
为什么？
For what?
求你了 听我说
Please, hear me.
没人听到你说话
Ain't nobody hearing you.
不妨冷静下来 享受旅程
May as well calm down and enjoy the ride.
就像我说的
Like I said.
结果没有改变
Outcome hasn't changed.
不
No.
请
Please.
哦 求你了
Oh, please, please.
请
Please.
打开
Abra.
托尼？
Tony?
请帮帮我 托尼
Help me, please, Tony.
上帝
God.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
他总是说你的...
Okay, he always said your...
你的大脑就像一台收音机
Your brain was like a radio.
你打电话时没人接电话 所以不要再打电话了
No one's answering when you call, so stop calling
听听
and just listen.
丹.
Dan, Dan.
帮助
Help.
你好
Hi.
丹
Dan.
他给你下药了吗？
Did he drug you?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我试试看 好吗？
I'm gonna try something, okay?
但你很虚弱 他挡住了你
But you're weak, he's blocking you.
我几乎听不到你说话
I barely hear you.
你得相信我 好吗？
You gotta trust me, okay?
好？
Okay?
又醒了 嗯？
Wake again, huh?
可能得在下一个休息点给你服药
May have to dose you at the next rest stop.
我们要去哪？
Where are we going?
你知道在哪儿
You know where.
妈的 我觉得有宿醉
Fuck, I feel hangover.
告诉你 这很好
Told you, it's good shit.
已经好几年没宿醉了 你知道我不会错过的
Haven't had hangover in years, and you know I don't miss it.
哪怕是一点点
Not even a little.
韦斯特 嗯？
West, huh?
远离主要道路 聪明
Stand off the major roads. Smart.
纽约皇冠维尔
Crownville, New York.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是杀死你朋友的人
I'm the guy that killed your friends.
很高兴见到你
It's nice to meet you.
整洁的把戏
Neat trick.
以前没见过这个
Haven't seen this one before.
想再看一个吗？
Wanna see one more?
别以为罗斯会太高兴 如果你拍奖？
Don't imagine Rose would be too happy if you shoot the prize?
我不认为罗斯会为此而高兴
I don't suppose Rose would be happy about any of this.
当那个女人发疯的时候
And when that woman gets mad.
嗯 那好吧
Well.
在我看来 你知道的足够知道 你可能想坐在这一个
Seems to me you know enough to know you might wanna sit this one out.
数你的祝福 继续你的方式
Count your blessings, go on your way.
有什么好笑的 朋友？
What's so funny, friend?
那只是傲慢
Well, it's just arrogance.
真的很傲慢
It's arrogance, really.
但是 如果你认为你会永远活着 那也是有道理的
But, makes sense if you think you gonna live forever.
站得住
Stands to reason.
当然 你不会系安全带的
Of course, you wouldn't wear your seat belt.
不！
No!
丹？
Dan?
我希望那很痛
I hope that hurts.
罗西
Rosie.
好多！
A lot!
你这个小婊子
You little bitch.
你都干了些什么？
What have you done?
好吧
All right, bitch-child.
All right.
对不起 多点了
Sorry, dosed up.
不 你赚到了
No, you earned it.
我们在哪？
Where are we?
俄亥俄州
Ohio.
-我们要去哪里？ -科罗拉多州
- Where are we going? - Colorado.
为什么选择科罗拉多州？
Why Colorado?
她会一直来的
She's gonna keep coming.
-我知道 -总是
- I know. - Always.
这只会结束 如果我们结束她 我不认为我们可以击败她
This only ends if we end her and I don't think we can beat her.
不是我们自己
Not by ourselves.
有个地方
There's a place.
这个地方 这对我们这样的人很危险
Place, that's dangerous for people like us.
你告诉我的地方？
The place you told me about?
-饥饿的地方？ -是的 没错
- Hungry place? - Yes, that's right.
如果太危险了 我们为什么要去那里？
If it's so dangerous, why would we go there?
如果对我们这样的人很危险
If it's dangerous for people like us,
我想这对像她这样的人是危险的
I expect it's dangerous for people like her.
也许更是如此
Maybe even more so.
好
Good.
她跟着 你知道的
She's following, you know.
是的 好 让她来
Yeah, good, let her.
我对你父亲感到抱歉
I'm sorry about your father.
对不起 你的朋友
Sorry about your friend.
那是我妈妈
That's my mom.
我该对她说什么？
What do I say to her?
嗨 妈妈
Hi, Mom.
哦 谢天谢地！
Oh, thank God!
阿布拉 你没事吧？你在哪里？
Abra, are you okay? Where are you?
我爱你
I love you.
当我们安全的时候 你打电话给她 告诉她在哪里可以找到我们
When we are safe you call her and tell where to find us.
我会的
I will.
好
Okay.
不要太远 上山
Not too much farther. Up in mountain.
下面是我们要做的
Here's what we gonna do.
你要呆在车里 让热火保持运转
You gonna stay in the car, keep the heat running.
如果你不需要的话 我不希望你在里面呆一分钟
I don't want you spending a minute inside there if you don't have to.
她只能从这里来
She can only come from here.
你会看到她英里外 容易
You'll see her mile out, easy.
你看到那边山上的灯光
You see lights on the mountain over there
你炸我 好吗？
you blast me, okay?
但我不想你去 直到她在这里
But I don't want you going in, not until she's here.
你在等我？
You're waiting with me?
-我不能 -为什么不？
- I can't - Why not?
我必须把它叫醒
I have to wake it up.
唤醒
Wakey-wakey.
慢夜 托伦斯先生
Slow night, Mr. Torrance.
我想 时间不会太长
Not for long, I imagine.
你是一个威士忌人 不是吗？
You are a whiskey man, are you not?
我曾经是 大多数时候
I was. Most of the time.
在房子里
On the house.
这是你的品牌
This was your brand.
杰克・丹尼尔斯
Jack Daniels.
我过去常在我们家看到瓶子
I used to see the bottles in our home.
在这一切之前 我们真正的家
Our real home before all this.
我闻到一次 它闻起来像火的东西 这
I smelled one once, it smelled like something on fire, which
我想是的
I suppose it was.
恐怕你把我和别人搞混了
I'm afraid you've confused me with someone else.
是劳埃德
It's Lloyd.
劳 埃 德
Lloyd.
我道歉 托伦斯先生
I apologize, Mr. Torrance.
我不知道每个人都在哪里 但它会回升
I don't know where everyone is, but it will pick up.
哦 我知道他们在哪儿
Oh, I know where they are.
你是对的
And you are right.
它会拿起
It'll pick up.
如果你不介意我说 托伦斯先生 你似乎
If you don't mind my saying, Mr. Torrance, you seem
放在
put upon.
放上？
Put upon?
陷入别人的问题
Pulled into other people's problems.
如果你不介意我说的话 我一直都能看到
I see it all the time, if you don't mind my saying.
所以我们住在佛罗里达
So we lived in Florida.
对不起？
I'm sorry?
妈妈和我.
Mom and I.
我们再也不想看到雪了
We never wanted to see snow again.
所以我们住在佛罗里达
So we lived in Florida.
小地方 但它是舒适的 我们很高兴
Tiny place, but it was comfortable and we were happy.
她死的时候我20岁
I was 20 when she died.
那时候
And back then,
我看到有人要死的时候 我看见苍蝇
I saw when someone was gonna die I saw flies,
黑苍蝇 我称之为死苍蝇
black flies, death flies I called them,
盘旋人们的脸
circling people's faces.
在最后一次醒来时 她被遮住了
And in those last wakes she was covered.
她的整张脸我几乎看不见她的眼睛
Her whole face. I could barely see her eyes.
我试着安慰她 但我几乎看不中她
And I tried to comfort her, but I could hardly look at her.
她看到了
And she saw that.
也许更可以推开这些不愉快的事情？
Maybe something more to push away such unpleasantries?
你不想听吗？她是你妻子
Don't you wanna hear about it? She was your wife.
我想你把我误认为是别人了
I think you've mistaken me for someone else.
-我只是个调酒师 -哦 是吗？
- I'm just a bartender. - Oh, yeah?
只是劳埃德酒保 在俯瞰酒店倾注喜悦？
Just Lloyd the Bartender, pouring joy at the Overlook hotel?
我会倾注任何你喜欢的 托伦斯先生
I'll pour whatever you like, Mr. Torrance.
男人喝一杯
Man takes a drink.
一杯饮料就喝
A drink takes the drink.
然后 饮料需要一个男人
And then the drink takes a man.
不是吗 爸爸？
Isn't it so, Dad?
医学
Medicine.
医学就是它
Medicine is what it is.
善意的关心
Bona fide cura.
头脑是一块黑板
The mind is a blackboard,
和这个
and this
是橡皮擦
is the eraser.
一个男人尝试
A man tries.
他提供
He provides.
但他包围了我的嘴
But he's surrounded my mouths.
并且有家人
And has family.
妻子 孩子
A wife, a kid.
那些嘴咬时间
Those mouths eat time.
他们在地球上吃你的日子
They eat your days on Earth.
把他吞没了
It is gobbled him up.
这足以让一个人生病
It's enough to make a man sick.
和这个
And this
是药
is the medicine.
告诉我 小狗
So tell me, pup.
你要吃药吗？
Are you gonna take your medicine?
我不是
I'm not.
丹
Dan.
她在这
She's here.
好
Okay.
这个地方病了
This place is sick.
像我的莫莫病一样生病
Sick like my MoMo was sick.
是癌症
It's cancer.
只是更糟
Only worse.
我们现在怎么办？
What do we do now?
我们会进去的 她会找到我们的
We'll get inside, she'll find us.
好 好 好
Well, well, well.
嘿 你好
Hi there.
当它启动 -运行
When it starts - run.
是的 你跑 亲爱的
Yes, you run, dear.
然后我会找到你
And then I will find you,
你会尖叫多年 直到你死
and you will scream for years until you die.
我们看看是谁在尖叫
We'll see who does the screaming.
我们确实会看到
We'll see indeed.
她是对的 你知道的
She's right, you know.
你应该害怕
You should be afraid.
为什么？
Why is that?
因为你不知道你站在哪里
Because you don't know where you're standing.
对不起 你是谁 帅哥？
I'm sorry, who are you, handsome?
是你杀了我的乌鸦 是吗？
You are the one who killed my Crow, aren't you?
去！
Go!
聪明
Clever.
你做了一些改进 是吗？
You've made some improvements, haven't you?
自从我上次在你心里
Since the last time I was in your mind.
你怎么知道我们不是你的？
How do you know we are not in yours?
你在哪里 小狗？
Where are you, pup?
你会死在这里
You gonna die here.
勇敢的话 亲爱的
Brave words, dear.
你才这么想吗？
Is that what you really think?
你要伤害我？
You gonna hurt me?
是的
Yes.
你知道 你让我想起我自己
You know, you remind me of myself.
我现在真的可以看到了
I can really see it now.
亲爱的 你的黑暗
You've got a darkness in you, dear.
但我认为你和我之间唯一的区别是时间
But I think the only difference between you and me is time.
你还不知道
You don't know yet
你做什么
what you do
更多的时间
for more time.
但答应你 亲爱的哦 你会惊讶的
But promise you, dear. Oh, you'd be surprised.
疼痛净化蒸汽
Pain purifies steam.
恐惧 所以...你明白
Fear too, so... You understand.
我年轻的时候就和你一样
I was just like you when I was younger.
如此特别
So special
和单独
and alone.
但我遇到了一个送我礼物的人――社区的目的
But I met someone who gave me the gift  - the purpose of community.
我可能给了你这么一份礼物
And I might've given you such a gift,
如果事情会有所不同的话
if things would've gone differently.
不？
No?
反对 不是吗？
Defying, aren't you?
很像我 你的头脑是如此...
So much like me, your mind it's so...
这不是你的头脑 对吗？
This isn't your mind, is it?
这根本不是你
This isn't you at all.
你只是诱饵？
You're just the bait?
足够！
Enough!
运行！
Run!
我们怎么会想你？
How the hell did we miss you?
我和我几年前就该见面了
You and I should've met years ago.
丹尼？
Danny?
那是你的名字 不是吗？
That's your name, isn't it?
嗯 当你的润滑油变老时 蒸汽会出事
Well, something happens to the steam when your lubes get older.
它被污染了
It gets polluted,
脏
dirty.
你知道吗？
You knew that?
我看到你全在油污
I see the grease all over you.
你的光芒并不完全一样
You don't shine quite the same.
我猜 长大后会破坏这一点
Growing up spoils that, I guess.
说真的 帅哥
Seriously, handsome.
你躲到哪里去了？
Where have you been hiding?
我可以给你报价
I can make you an offer.
我很少提出这个提议
An offer I rarely make.
哦 是的？我等不及了
Oh, yeah? I can't wait.
这么有天赋的男孩
Such a gifted boy,
隐藏他的光在丛林下这么久
hiding his light under bushwa for so long.
你可以活得很长 也活得很好
You can live a long long time, live well too.
放纵自己
Indulge yourself.
没有后果
No consequences.
没有宿醉
No hangovers.
吃得好 活得长
Eat well, live long.
你一定很孤独 做最后一个
You must be lonely, being the last one.
我是说世界上最后一个
I mean the last one in the world.
亲爱的 我不是最后一个 离它很远
Sweetie, I'm not the last, far from it.
我只是最漂亮的
I'm just the prettiest.
我想你知道我的答案
I assume you know my answer.
可惜
Pity.
那么 我们是否这样做？
So, are we doing this or not?
哦 亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
哦 看那个吧？
Oh, look at that, huh?
我好像已经挖了你的动脉
I seem to have nicked your Femoral artery there.
你要流血致死吗？
You gonna bleed to death, huh?
我的 你脾气多
My my, what a temper you have.
这么多火
So much fire.
这么浪费！
Such a waste!
或者也许不是
Or maybe not.
哦 该死的
Oh, damn.
即使在你这个年龄
Even at your age.
太好了
It's so good.
你尝起来像威士忌
You taste like whiskey.
丹尼！
Danny!
丹尼男孩！
Danny boy!
太恐怖了
So much terror.
一辈子？
All your life, huh?
美味
Delicious.
别伤害我！
Don't hurt me!
哦 该死的
Oh, damn.
什么 不是孤独的吗？
What, are not alone in there?
你在隐瞒什么？
What are you hiding, huh?
那些是什么？
What's in those?
特别的东西 嗯？
Something special, huh?
它们并不特别
They are not special.
他们正在挨饿
They are starving.
不！
No!
你好 丹尼
Hello, Danny.
来和我们一起玩吧
Come and play with us.
永远
Forever
and ever,
和永远
and ever.
丹叔叔？
Uncle Dan?
丹叔叔 完成了吗？
Uncle Dan, is it done?
她死了吗？
Is she dead?
很棒的派对 不是吗？
Great party, isn't it?
打开！
Abra!
试试看
Try it.
你在这儿
There you are.
打开
Abra.
你一直很坏
You've been very very bad.
你不是丹叔叔
You are not Uncle Dan.
你是一个面具 一张假脸
You are a mask, a false face.
我还能是谁？
Who else could I be?
你是酒店 但他还在那里
You're The Hotel, but he's still in there.
面具关闭然后
Mask off then.
你为什么笑？
Why are you smiling?
因为你不知道你站在哪里
Because you don't know where you're standing.
我知道这些大厅就像我自己的脸 孩子
I know these halls like my own face, child.
我是说你站在那具尸体里
I mean the body you're standing in.
你穿的脸
The face you're wearing.
那是丹・托伦斯 你不认识他
That's Dan Torrance, and you don't know him.
丹・托伦斯？
Dan Torrance?
丹・托伦斯
Dan Torrance.
他一到这儿就停了一站
Made one stop as soon as he got here -
锅炉房
to the boiler room.
你在这儿
There you are.
你应该跑的
You were supposed to run.
我不想离开你
I didn't wanna leave you.
我正好是我应该去的地方
I'm exactly where I'm supposed to be.
我再也撑不下去了 阿布拉 你需要跑
I can't hold it off for much longer, Abra, you need to run.
不！
No!
没有你我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere without you.
我必须关上我们身后的门 对吗？
I have to close the door behind us, right?
跑 跑！
Run, run!
来吧 丹叔叔
Come on, Uncle Dan.
离开那里
Get out of there.
加油
Come on.
火势迅速蔓延
The fire spread fast,
摧毁酒店
destroying the hotel.
净化它
Purifying it.
我几乎能听见
I could almost hear it
尖叫
screaming.
我能听到它死去
I could hear it dying,
和内心深处我知道
and deep inside I knew.
我知道你没事
I knew you were okay.
很抱歉 我把你置于危险之中
I'm sorry I put you in danger.
这是唯一的办法
It was the only way.
我知道
I know.
你认为她是对的吗？
Do you think she was right,
当她说她不是最后一个？
when she said she wasn't the last one?
世界是饥饿的地方
The world's the hungry place.
一个黑暗的地方
A dark place.
也许还有更多的人 或者像他们一样的东西 或者更糟的 但是...
Maybe there're more of them, or things like them or worse, but...
也有更多的人像你一样
There are more people like you too.
站着的人
People who stand.
我告诉你们 当我第一次见到你
I told you, when I first met you
我告诉你应该躲起来
I told you that you should hide.
你应该低着头
That you should keep your head down.
把你的光芒放在视线之外
Keep your shine out of sight.
但我错了
But I was wrong.
闪亮 阿布拉・斯通
Shine on, Abra Stone.
你发光
You shine on.
晚餐准备好了
Dinner's ready.
你在跟谁说话？
Who were you talking to?
没人
No one.
那不是真的
That's not true.
我在和丹说话
I was talking to Dan.
我们继续 之后
We go on, after.
我们继续
We go on.
他没事
And he's okay.
爸爸也是
So is Daddy.
他真的是
He really is.
好
Good.
你来了 甜心？
You're coming, sweetheart?
一会儿就来
In a minute.